In this step I'm going to show you how to cut and prepare the wire that goes in the ears of the animal purse as well as the strap.
First you're going to need your strap.
You're going to need your ear shape and you're going to need your floral wire.
This is 24 gage wire and this is a little smaller.
Either one will work well.
So now I want you to take your wire and measure it all the way around your ear.
And you don't have to go around the bottom.
Just around three sides is fine.
But you want to make sure it goes around the edges.
And it doesn't have to be exact.
And you can leave a little extra on the bottom.
Also use scissors.
Not your fabric scissors.
Use your junk scissors to cut this wire.
So there we go.
It can come off a little bit but you want to make sure it's around the edges because that's what's going to hold up the ear on your purse.
Also, this wire is too short for my strap but the paddle wire is great.
We undo that, measure it out.
Again, you can make it a little bit longer than your strap is.
Cut it.
And again, use not your good fabric scissors.
Use other scissors or wire cutters to cut this.
And there you go.
You have your wire for your strap and your wire for your ear.